What are you doing to me?
Where am I?
Oh, shoot.
Oh, lie down.
No, it's not coming back!
That's the point!
I'm down here looking through this,
all this stuff!
Now, who is that?
I don't recognize any of this.
Oh, the money. Right.
Oh, my!
How did you get my.... My!
I told you to stay in the car.
You need to bring me back
that kid's head...
Get out of here.
What are you doing?
What is the French word for ''stakeout''?
That's Eamon. I'll talk to him.
We're leaving.
It's me, Marie. Wow...
Mommy is away for two days.
You were up early.
Who are you?
Let's ask Marie what she wants.
I don't think she cares at all.
What are you talking about?
You don't know what you're doing, do you?
You don't have a clue!
You're a total catastrophe!
And, if it kills me,
you'll tell me how this happened.
I can send Nicky to do that!
You picked the yacht
as the  strike point!